# **PIYUSHA JADHAV**

ADDRESS: B-301 SHREE PUSHPA APT, DATTAWADI, KALWA (W), THANE – 400605

Mobile No: 720827-8494

Email: pj.piyu@gmail.com

I have completed my Masters in Applied Psychology specializing in Clinical Psychology. Working as a psychologist as well as completing my internship and gaining experience by working with various population, have made me capable in psychometric testing and implementation of therapeutic practices.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

 Centre for Assessment, Remediation and Therapy- Psychologist (September 2018- currently)

Centre for Assessment, Remediation and Therapy is a mental health clinic especially working for schools and colleges. I am a psychologist in the centre specifically working with St Mary's ICSE School, Koparkhairne. The role entails me to identify and test for academic, behavioural, social problems of students between the ages of 4 to 17. The role also entails me to test for cognitive deficit in students. It also includes administering different kinds of test related to various issues. The job also requires working with parents and teachers to formulate intervention plans. It also includes taking remediation for students having academic issues based upon basic screening and psychoeducational assessment. The job also includes career guidance and counselling using psychometric tests in order to guide students choose the correct career path. The job also entails taking seminars of teachers, parents and students related to various informative topics. The role also includes making weekly, monthly and yearly reports.

Dharmaveer Anand Dighe Zidd Shala- Psychologist (July 2018 – September 2018)

Jidd Shala is a government run school for special children. I was volunteering in the school for 2 days a week. My role was of a psychologist. The role entailed me to identify and test for intellectual disability, testing for behaviour and cognitive deficit and working with parents and teachers to formulate plans to implement interventions.

• Sion Hospital – Observership (Nov 2017- Dec 2017)

Observersihip entailed observing psychiatrist and psychologist working with different population. It entailed observing session of mental health patient and learning various intervention.

 Chattarapati Shivaji Maharaj Hospital, Kalwa – Intern Clinical Psychologist (August 2017- October 2017)

Work there entailed directly testing clients from different population after taking detailed case history and MSE. It also included psycho-educating the clients and guardians and recommending interventions when needed. Presentation of the cases to the concerned psychiatrist was also expected as well as reviewing the testing result and interventions.

#### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:**

YEAR	DEGREE COMPLETED	UNIVERSITY	SUBJECTS	GPA/%/GRADE
2007	10TH	SSC	GENERAL	82%
2009	12TH	HSC	SCIENCE	72%
2016	TYBA	MUMBAI UNIVERSITY	PSYCHOLOGY	A GRADE
2018	M.A(PSYCHOLOGY)	MUMBAI UNIVERSITY	APPLIED PSYCHOOGY	7 GPA

#### **RESEARCH WORK:**

- MA dissertation: Body Image Concerns and its Impact among Gay Men In depth qualitative interviews of 12 gay men was carried out that highlighted the issues faced by gay men regarding their body and how did it impact them, in the Indian context.
- Designed an experiment to study the effect of context on incidental vocabulary learning.
- Designed a psychometric test for measuring body image issues.

### ADDITIONAL CERTIFICATION:

- Basic RECBT course by Invivo
- Advance RECBT course by Invivo
- Transactional Analysis with Gestalt Therapy by Mind Mandala.
- Gay Affirmative Counselling Therapy by IPH.
- Counselling Course by IPH.

#### **OTHER ACTIVITIES:**

- Attended the seminar 'Psycho-magnum' in the year 2015-2016.
- Attended the seminar 'Psychiatric Issues in LGBT Groups' by Indian Psychiatric Association on 10th March, 2018.
- Attended the seminar 'Mental Health Awareness' by Bombay Psychiatric Society on 10th October

## SKILLS:

- Psychometric testing
- History taking and MSE
- Neuropsychology
- suicide risk assessment
- counselling skills
- Qualitative/quantitative research

- Projective assessment
- SPSS/PSPP
- R software
- Open sesame
- •Remediation
- Seminar conduction